(Howard:)What's up?
(Stuart:)Uh, well, I know
(Stuart:)the remodel is coming up,
so I thought I'd make it easy
(Stuart:)on you guys
and find my own place.
Wow. (chuckles)
(Howard:)I thought I was done
getting lucky tonight.
(Bernadette:)So, when are you
thinking of moving?
(Stuart:)Uh, actually,
I already found an apartment,
(Stuart:)so in a couple of days.
(Bernadette:)Oh. Okay.
(Bernadette:)Sorry to see you go?
(Amy:)Okay, well,
thank you guys for everything.
I-I really appreciate it.
You're very welcome.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Howard:)What?
(Stuart:)Hmm, I just have never been
in this room while you're awake.
(door closes)
(Sheldon:)What are you doing?
(Raj:)Uh, making sure the telescope's
camera is white-field balanced.